Fa-la-la, fa-la-la
Fa-la-la, ahhh
Deck the halls with boughs of holly
冬青树枝装点大厅
'Tis the season to be jolly
让这季节满是欢愉
Christmas day's around the corner
圣诞佳节即将来临
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la
Light the hearth, let's make things warmer
燃起壁炉  驱寒取暖
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la
Bring the tree in front and center
圣诞之树摆在当中
Fa-la-la, la-la-la, la-la-la
Gleaming bright in all its splendor
闪耀之中尽显华丽
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la
Boughs of fur upon the mantle
毛绒树枝置于毯上
Shining stars, each dancing candle
火星闪烁烛光摇曳中
Draped in ribbons red and silver
系上彩带红和银色
Joy upon us is delivered
心头喜悦已经送到
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la
Fa-la-la, la-la-la
Fa-la-la-la
Wrap our gifts in colored paper
把礼品用彩纸打包
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
Tie with bows and store for later
彩绳打结存贮备用
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
Set the feast upon the table
美味佳肴端上餐桌
Fa-la-la, la-la-la, la-la-la
Friends together, willing, able
朋友欢聚  其乐融融
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la
Fa-la-la, fa-la-la
Fa-la-la, ahhh
翻译
轮回
润色
包子
校对
傻猫
背景图绘制
缤纷彩彩
时间轴
Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看